

My Contact

didorchuka@gmail.com

+380503921490

Oleksandr Didorchuk

AlexandrDidorchuk

Odessa, Ukraine

Tech Skill

- HTML5
- CSS3/SASS
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- REST
- API
- GITParcel
-
- Webpack
- Node.js
- MongoDB

Soft Skill

- Communicative
- Responsibility
- · Attention to detail
- Eager to learn
- Teamwork
- Organized

Languages

- Ukraine native
- English intermediate
- Russian native

OLEKSANDR DIDORCHUK

Junior Front-End Developer

Summary

I am a Front-end developer looking for opportunities to use my knowledge and contribute to projects aimed at helping people make their lives and businesses more convenient and efficient. I know HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React well.

I have experience working in a team, I easily communicate with people, and I know how to solve complex problems, thanks to more than 15 years of experience in the trade. I have much experience dealing with customers, and I know exactly how important it is to deliver a great product to the customer in the established lines and be responsible for it.

Project Experience

Recipes - So Yummy Link

[React, Redux, Styled-components, MUI, Axios, Webpack, GIT]

Team project. Role: developer.

"What to cook?" is not only a recipe app, it is, in fact, your cookbook. You can add your recipes to save them for the future. The application has been developed taking into account the adaptive layout from mobile devices to desktops.

Phonebook Link [JS, React, Webpack, GIT]

Phonebook app that allows registration, login, and updating of users' contacts, as well as working with a private collection of contacts.

Filmoteka Link

[HTML5, SASS, JS, Parcel, GIT, Rest API, AJAX]

Team project. Role: developer.

Application for search movie info. Search input logic and render movie cards. Work with Local storage on the library page.

IceCream Link [HTML5, SASS, JS, Parcel, GIT]

Team project. Role: developer.

Site for ice cream business with responsive/adaptive layout. Contacts section with modal window and request form for customers.

Web-studio Link [HTML5, CSS3, SASS]

Own project. Web studio site with adaptive, mobile-first layout.

Work Experience

Own company | 03/2011 - present

Own business in the field of wholesale and small wholesale trade, and transport services.

Responsibilities:

- communication with both suppliers of goods and buyers;
- logistics;
- reporting;
- using the IC program.

The result of the work done was the creation of a small enterprise with a hard-working team and excellent teamwork. This allowed us to significantly expand our customer base and increase the company's profits.

For me, this is a great life experience with invaluable skills in communication, responsibility, determination, and stress resistance.

Company "B.B.C." | 12/2006 - 02/2011

Sales Representative

Responsibilities - direct sales of food products to retail outlets.

Increased the client base by 60%.

Increased the company's income by 25%.

Education

Odessa State Agrarian University

Specialist in growing agricultural crops | 2000 - 2005

IT school Go It

Fullstack Developer | 2022 - 2023 Certificate

Udemy <u>Certificate</u>